Theme parks are fun.
They were originally created by our reptilian rulers to distract us from the invasion
Just like anime and waffles! But recently more and more people are discovering the truth so today
I'm going to show the lizards how to build a theme park
Guaranteed to distract those tasty humans
First the best theme park needs the best theme
We can all agree that when we think cinematic masterpieces
we think the mummy movies
So an Ancient Egypt theme!
Ah, no egyptian props. We'll have to improvise
Here's my pyramid, looks good, and my sphinx looks
Yeah
This will not work
Maybe a 1900s survival theme. What's a cute and fun trend from the 20th century we can resurrect
Hrmm... Exactly!
Communism. Welcome to the people's park. Entrance is free!
Actually, it's mandatory
Please visit our gray roller coasters
Our milk shake stand serves only milk as milk shakes are bourgeoisie propaganda
Drinking them makes you an enemy of the revolution
Stop complaining that the lines are too long
And don't you know that the landowners makes
a lot of money, Jesus!
New plan, screw the workers, I'mma make a park for rich people
Welcome to offshore resort seven Michelin Star restaurants, and one exotic meat restaurant
Does it serve animals close to extinction? Noo
We made them extinct
You see that? That's a Porta potty!
And finally a converted 4.5 billion dollar aircraft carrier, it's fully armed. That's how we deal with the protesters
Why is no one showing up? One ticket is only 1 million?
We're screwed, so that set us back billions
Good thing we were too big to fail
We'll use our bailout money to make a park that is guaranteed to make money, by stealing something that works
Welcome to Disney Universal World Resort Land!
Ever wanted to see Alice in
Jurassic Park, or how about Snow White and the Seven
Transformers? Finally we can combine Star Wars with a good franchise!
and I received a copyright strike
Inside the game! I'm impressed. So maybe not steal an idea. Maybe get inspired.
Delos Incorporated has excited a world with their
Westworld because you can go to an extinct age and kill kids!
We here at the Kilian Experience
Cannot afford that
But we can recreate the extinct age excitements with our brand new
Video Rental World be amazed as our lifelike host help you rent the mosque
be amazed as our lifelike hosts help you rent The Mask
You can follow this host and he will lead you to a giant octopus
We don't know if they really existed as not much information is left from the video rental age
It failed miserably because someone started Video Streaming World. New theme!
I like snow, so I want a snow theme, but that's too generic
What if we have this white snow and we'll add an electricity theme and we'll call it
white powe- No, n-no.
snow
S N O W
what about
Snow-
-den! I'll just read everyone's opinions and the - Wait.
I got an email from the NSA please don't make a video mocking us. We are very sensitive
How did they- they are good! so the government shut us down and I'm tired of their constant interference
Hello, I'm Kilian Experience
And I'm here to ask you a question - is a theme park good because of it's theme?
No, says the man in Copenhagen, it's because of age!
No, says the man in Orlando, it's because of brand recognition!
No, says the man in Shenzhen, it's because of cheap labor!
But I created something different. I created Rapture!
...Land.
This is not a great way to run a theme park. I guess the point of rapture was that it was objectivist, so instead
i'm making Libertarian Kingdom! the ruler - that would be me - is hands-off
this is not a great way to run a theme park
screw this I'm building a piñata zoo
Because I succeeded with my mission while watching this you completely forgot about the reptilians
all your base are belong to us